<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on RayG</title>
    <link>https://ray-g.github.io/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on RayG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 21:23:29 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ray-g.github.io/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Notebook Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://ray-g.github.io/others/jupyter-notebook-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 21:23:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ray-g.github.io/others/jupyter-notebook-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description> Jupyter Notebook has 2 Modes: Edit Mode and Command Mode.
NOTE: If you are in Edit Mode, there is a pencil at the upper-right.
Switch between modes Enter to enter Edit Mode from Command Mode
ESC to return Command Mode from Edit Mode
Show and edit shortcuts Shortcuts can be show by Help -&amp;gt; Keyboard Shortcuts
And the shortcuts is also editable Help -&amp;gt; Edit Keyboard Shortcuts
Default Shortcuts Shortcuts in Command Mode    Key Action     F find and replace   Ctrl-Shift-F open the command palette   Ctrl-Shift-P open the command palette   P open the command palette   Enter Enter Edit Mode   Ctrl-Enter run selected cells   Shift-Enter run cell and select below   Alt-Enter run cell and insert below   Y change cell to code   M change cell to markdown   R change cell to raw   1 change cell to heading 1   2 change cell to heading 2   3 change cell to heading 3   4 change cell to heading 4   5 change cell to heading 5   6 change cell to heading 6   Shift-Space scroll notebook up   Space scroll nobebook down   K select cell above   Up select cell above   J select cell below   Down select cell below   Shift-K extend selected cells above   Shift-Up extend selected cells above   Shift-J extend selected cells below   Shift-Down extend selected cells below   A insert cell above   B insert cell below   X cut selected cells   C copy selected cells   V paste cells below   Shift-V paste cells above   Z undo cell deletion   D, D delete selected cells   Shift-M merge selected cells, or current cell with cell below if only one cell is selected   Ctrl-S save and checkpoint   S save and checkpoint   L toggle line numbers   Shift-L toggles line numbers in all cells, and persist the setting   O toggle output of selected cells   Shift-O toggle output scrolling of selected cells   H show keyboard shorcuts   I, I interrupt the kernel   0, 0 restart the kernel (with dialog)   Ctrl-V dialog for paste from system clipboard   Esc close the pager   Q close the pager    Shortcuts in Edit Mode    Key Action     Esc enter command mode   Ctrl-M enter command mode   Ctrl-Shift-F open the command palette   Ctrl-Shift-P open the command palette   Ctrl-Enter run selected cells   Alt-Enter run cell and insert below   Shift-Enter run cell and select below   Ctrl-S Save and Checkpoint   Up move cursor up   Down move cursor down   Ctrl-Shift-Minus split cell at cursor   Tab code completion or indent   Shift-Tab tooltip   Ctrl-] indent   Ctrl-[ dedent   Ctrl-A select all   Ctrl-Y redo   Ctrl-Z undo   Ctrl-/ comment   Ctrl-D delete whole line   Ctrl-U undo selection   Alt-U redo selection   Insert toggle overwrite flag   Ctrl-Home go to cell start   Ctrl-Up go to cell start   Ctrl-End go to cell end   Ctrl-Down go to cell end   Ctrl-Left go one word left   Ctrl-Right go one word right   Ctrl-Backspace delete work before   Ctrl-Delete delete work after    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Snippts</title>
      <link>https://ray-g.github.io/others/git-snippts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:05:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ray-g.github.io/others/git-snippts/</guid>
      <description> Fetch all submodules after clone From the root of the repo just run:
git submodule update --init  Sync fork # Step 1 clone fork git clone git@github.com:&amp;lt;USERNAME&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;FORK-REPO&amp;gt;.git # Step 2, cd to the repo git remote add upstream git://github.com/ORIGINAL-DEV-USERNAME/REPO-YOU-FORKED-FROM.git git fetch upstream git pull upstream master git push  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up The Blog</title>
      <link>https://ray-g.github.io/others/setting-up-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 13:51:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ray-g.github.io/others/setting-up-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>This blog is built with Hugo and hosted on Github.
Setting up Hugo site Install Hugo First we should have a Hugo installed, Install Hugo, or just download the binary from github.com/gohugoio/hugo.
After Hugo installed, try verify it.
$ hugo version Hugo Static Site Generator v0.41 linux/amd64 BuildDate: 2018-05-25T16:57:20Z  Create a New Site Hugo can generate layout of a new site very easy:
$ hugo new site hugo-blog Congratulations!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>